
=== laksa bogor bowl ===
  Laksa Bogor 2.JPG
    A travelling cart vendor selling Laksa Bogor, a laksa variant from Bogor, West Java, 
  Laksa Bogor 3.JPG
    A travelling cart vendor selling Laksa Bogor, a laksa variant from Bogor, West Java, 
  Laksa Bogor 1.JPG
    Laksa Bogor, a laksa variant from Bogor, West Java, Indonesia. The boiling hot thick 
  Laksa Bogor 4.JPG
    A travelling cart vendor selling Laksa Bogor, a laksa variant from Bogor, West Java, 

=== laksa indonesia ===
  Laksa Jakarta.JPG
    Laksa, Jakarta, Indonesia
  Stir Fried Squid with Laksa Paste.jpg
    Quite an interesting dish of stir fried squid with ÚôÂÚÆêþ▓ë/ÞÇüÚ╝áþ▓ë(rice noodles) with laksa p
  Laksa.jpg
    Banjar laksa, from Banjarmasin, South Kalimantan. Laksa variants native in the culina
  Laksa Bogor 2.JPG
    A travelling cart vendor selling Laksa Bogor, a laksa variant from Bogor, West Java, 
  Laksa Bogor 3.JPG
    A travelling cart vendor selling Laksa Bogor, a laksa variant from Bogor, West Java, 
  Laksa Bogor 1.JPG
    Laksa Bogor, a laksa variant from Bogor, West Java, Indonesia. The boiling hot thick 
  Laksa Bogor 4.JPG
    A travelling cart vendor selling Laksa Bogor, a laksa variant from Bogor, West Java, 
  Chicken curry served in an Indonesian restaurant; February 2010.jpg
    A bowl of warm chicken curry, consisted of rich creamy coconut milk and mellow lemong
  Laksa Betawi 1.jpg
    Laksa Betawi, Jakarta-style laksa served during Kampoeng Legenda Food Festival in Mal
  Laksa Betawi 3.jpg
    Laksa Betawi, Jakarta-style laksa served during Kampoeng Legenda Food Festival in Mal
  Laksa Betawi 2.jpg
    Laksa Betawi, Jakarta-style laksa served during Kampoeng Legenda Food Festival in Mal
  Laksa Rancakalong Sumedang.jpg
    Laksa Rancakalong Sumedang

=== ayam pop padang nasi ===

=== ayam goreng padang ===
  Ayam pop.JPG
    Pop chicken at Padang restaurant
  Hati ayam petai masakan Padang.JPG
    Chicken liver with sambal
  Sotoayam.jpg
    dalah makanan khas Indonesia seperti sop yang terbuat dari kaldu daging dan sayuran. 
